### Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy

KRAMER LABORATORIES, INC. PRIVACY POLICY
----------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy applies to personal information that may be collected by Kramer Laboratories, Inc. (“Kramer Laboratories, Inc.,” “we”, “us”). Kramer Laboratories, Inc. values your trust and respects your privacy. We are committed to responsibly protecting your personal information and only using your personal information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

By doing business with or interacting with Kramer Laboratories, Inc. in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time after the March 20, 2017, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described.

#### Who Do I Contact With Questions, Concerns and to Opt Out of Certain Features?

If you would like to contact us about anything related to this policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://funginail.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[\[email protected\]](https://funginail.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

#### What Personal Information Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Collect?

Personal information is information that can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Such information may include your:

Name

Postal or shipping address

Telephone number

E-mail address

Payment information (like credit or debit card number and billing address)

#### Why Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Collect Personal Information?

We collect your personal information in an effort to provide you with an enhanced experience and as may be necessary to administer our business. It allows us to answers any of your questions or concerns, and provide you with easy access to our newsletters, products and services. Your personal information also allows us to communicate with you about updates, special offers, promotions and other marketing programs that may be of interest to you.

#### **How Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Collect Personal Information?**

#### Information You Provide

As a general matter, you may browse on our website without submitting personal information to

Kramer Laboratories, Inc.. However, in order to answer your questions, send you our newsletter or provide marketing services such as coupons, special offers or surveys, we ask for certain personal information (“Personal Information”).

#### Information Automatically Collected

There are circumstances in which we automatically receive and collect personal information from you. The most common of these circumstances include “cookies.”

#### Cookies

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. uses “cookies,” small data files stored on your computer’s web browser, or other passive means of data collection. Cookies are used to personalize your visit, remember your preferences and online browsing. You can adjust your web browser to accept or reject cookies.

#### Outside sources

Also, to improve our marketing and the content of our website we collect aggregate, non- personal data like Internet Service Provider’s domain name, the referring URL and the web pages and information you access on our site. We use this information to analyze visitors’ behavior in the aggregate to improve our web site. This information does not include personal information.

#### How Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Use The Personal Information That It Collects?

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. uses your personal information to provide you with a superior customer experience and to administer our business. For example, the personal information we collect may be used to:

Contact you about products, services, events or promotions you may be interested in, except where prohibited by law;

Enhance your online experience, improve the content and navigation of our website, and customize content, layout or offers; and

Protect the security of our website and to analyze trends and statistics.

#### Information collected from visitors outside the United States

If you are visiting Kramer Laboratories, Inc. from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information may be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country.

**By doing business or interacting with Kramer Laboratories, Inc., you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by Kramer Laboratories, Inc., and understand that such information will be stored and processed in accordance with U.S. law**.

#### Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Share My Personal Information?

Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is important to Kramer Laboratories, Inc.. When appropriate, Kramer Laboratories, Inc. shares personal information among our family of companies (not including third party affiliates) to help provide you with better service and information about our products and services that we believe would be of interest to you, except where prohibited by law.

We share select information with the service providers we use to help manage our business for things like:

Market research

Fulfilling promotions

Name and address verification

E-mail management

To host our website, data storage or ad servers

These service providers only have access to the personal information they need to perform their services, and do not have the right to use personal information in ways not authorized by Kramer Laboratories, Inc.. They are prohibited from using this personal information for their own marketing purposes and are not allowed to share this personal information with anyone other than Kramer Laboratories, Inc..

**If you prefer not to have your personal information shared with these organizations please contact us at** [\[email protected\]](https://funginail.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**[\[email protected\]](https://funginail.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)****. In order for Kramer Laboratories, Inc. to confirm your identity and ensure your wishes are honored, requests sent to Kramer Laboratories, Inc. email addresses must be sent using the email account to which the request pertains.**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we determine, in our judgment, that it is necessary to (a) comply with the law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request; (b) enforce the terms of any of our polices; or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Kramer Laboratories, Inc., its employees or customers. This may include assistance in fraud protection or investigation.

We could also disclose or transfer your personal information to a successor entity in the event of a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate with respect to Kramer Laboratories, Inc. or our affiliated companies.

#### How Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Secure My Personal Information?

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. takes substantial and appropriate security measures to help to safeguard your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure. We have

a variety of current technologies, managerial safeguards, protocols and processes in place to protect the security and privacy of your personal information_**.**_

We update and test our security technology on an ongoing basis. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to those employees who need to know that information to provide benefits or services to you. In addition, we train our employees about the importance of confidentiality and maintaining the privacy and security of your information. We commit to taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce our employees’ privacy responsibilities.

We want you to feel confident whenever you visit us on our website or otherwise. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards designed to protect such information, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will remain secure in all circumstances.

#### How Can I Opt-Out of Receiving Communication From Kramer Laboratories, Inc.?

If you have submitted your email in order to receive the Kramer Laboratories, Inc. newsletter or updates, you can opt-out of theses communications by clicking on the “Remove My Subscription” link included in the email body of all email notifications and marketing emails provided by Kramer Laboratories, Inc.

#### How Does Kramer Laboratories, Inc. Respect My Choices About My Personal Information?

By providing personal information to Kramer Laboratories, Inc., including through kramerlabs.com, fungi-nail.com, nailner.com, safetussin.com, you acknowledge and agree that you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, use, retention and disclosure of such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. At Kramer Laboratories, Inc., we respect your privacy and will honor your choice to opt out of marketing communications or the sharing of personal information with our partners.

**If you wish to be removed from our marketing emails, calling or postal mailing lists please contact us at the contact information listed above. In addition you may remove yourself from our marketing e-mail list by clicking****here****, or on the unsubscribe link that is at the bottom of each marketing email. Please include your name and mailing address in any correspondence.**

For e-mail list removal, it may take up to 10 business days to process your request. For calling list removal, it may take up to 30 days to process your request.

For postal mailing list removal, it may take up to 6-8 weeks to process your request as our customer personal information is collected in advance due to printing schedules.

#### Links to Other, Third Party Web Sites

Occasionally we may provide links on our website to third party sites we at Kramer Laboratories, Inc. believe you may be interested in. These sites are independent from Kramer Laboratories, Inc. and have their own separate privacy policies. Whenever you click on links on Kramer Laboratories, Inc. website that take you to a third party website, you will be subject to the third party’s privacy policies, and not Kramer Laboratories, Inc.’s. We recommend that you review their privacy polices before you visit these sites.

#### Children’s Privacy

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect or solicit any personal information from children under the age of

18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account. Should we learn that

someone under the age of 18 has provided any personal information to or on Kramer Laboratories, Inc.’s website, we will remove that information as soon as possible.

#### California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, Kramer Laboratories, Inc.’s customers living in the State of California can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of personal information shared with third parties and used for direct marketing purposes and the name and address of the third parties that received such personal information. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this

notice, please submit a request to the contact information listed above. Please allow 30 days for a response.

#### Changes To Kramer Laboratories, Inc.’s Privacy Policy

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be posted on our website. We encourage you to check Kramer Laboratories, Inc.’s Privacy Policy when you visit our website.

**Kramer Laboratories, Inc.**

Kramer Laboratories, Inc. is a market leader in self-care, innovation and product development.

Learn more at [KramerLabs.com](http://kramerlabs.com/)

**Other Kramer Products**

**Kramer Laboratories, Inc.**

Toll-Free: 800.824.4894

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://funginail.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

440 US Highway 22, Suite 210

Bridgewater, NJ 08807
